西蒙・斯特恩这个名字你耳熟吗
You recognize the name Simon Stern?
他是纽约最大的毒贩子之一
He's one of the biggest nightlife investors in New York.
你那里有几个屁股挺翘
You got some fine-ass-looking girls
招待酒水的妞啊
serving drinks in there, by the way.
有一个红头发的 长得挺高... 她叫什么
There was this one red hair, tall... what's her name?
她叫"别动我们的脱衣女郎" 混蛋
Her name is don't touch the merchandise, motherfucker.
不是每个人都理解我们 杰米
Not everybody understands us, Jamie.
我哪里也不去 塔莎
I'm not going anywhere, Tasha.
我就留在这里 就在你想让我呆的地方
I'm stuck here, right where you want me.
我们要举行一次会议 我坐在桌子这边
We have us a meeting. I sit across the table.
直视着那些混蛋们的眼睛
I look all those motherfuckers in the eye,
然后我一定要找出派杀手杀我的混蛋
and I'll find out who's hitting me once and for all.
在那之前 谁也拿不着货
Until then, no one gets product.
洛沃斯的贩毒商
The Lobos' New York distributor
要会见他的团伙了
is meeting with his network.
所以他不仅不给我们弄货了
So not only is he not getting us product,
还对我们不屑一顾
but he doesn't respect us enough to be here.
FBI 举起双手
FBI! Let me see your hands!
你为什么要在最后一刻
Why you switch up the spot for the meeting
更换见面的地方
at the last second?
再怎么谨慎也不为过
You can never be too careful.
阿尼巴尔这混蛋去哪儿了
Where the fuck is Anibal?
我这些年没有一天不想你
I never stopped thinking about you all these years.
你好呀
Hey, hey.
这就像是我们又回到了十五岁
It feels like we're 15 again
从我父母家里溜出来的感觉
sneaking out of my parents' apartment.
才不是那样呢
It ain't like that.
我司机把车停到后边了
My driver's parked in the back.
当然了 和我们十五岁的时候一样
Of course, just like when we were 15.
我本可以打车的
I could've taken a cab.
你把我想成什么样的人了
What kind of guy do you think I am?
- 呃 安琪 我们之间... - 怎么了
- Um, Angie, are we... - What?
还可以吧
Okay, I guess.
我觉得比"可以"好多了
Better than okay, I think.
晚安 安琪
Good night, Angie.
晚安 杰米
Good night, Jamie.
# 一目了然 一目了然 #
Stand out a mile, stand out a mile
# 但是弟弟 若无欢笑 #
but, brother, you're never
# 你便不算 盛装打扮 #
fully dressed without a smile
雷娜 注意那个变调 好吗
Watch that turn now, Raina, okay?
- 好的 - # 若无欢笑 #
- Mm-hmm. - You're never
# 你便不算 盛装打扮 #
fully dressed without a smile
多坚持一会
Hold that out a little.
- 你听起来棒极了 - 谢谢
- You sound really good. - Thank you.
如果你按照我教你的做 你也会的
And you will, too, if you do what I said.
早上好啊 瞌睡虫
Good morning, sleepyhead.
早上好
Morning.
我没听见你昨晚回来了
I didn't hear you come in last night.
是啊 监盘人昨天休息了
Yeah, the count was off,
所以我们留下来确保夜店正常运作
so we stayed to make sure it was right.
然后你们用这么美妙的歌喉唤醒了我
And then y'all woke me up with those beautiful voices.
你继续这么唱下去
You keep singing like that,
我保证你会领先别人的
I guarantee you'll get the lead.
五年级的学生从来获不了奖
The fifth graders never get it.
是的 但是亲爱的 他们从没
Yeah, but, baby girl, they never seen
见过像我雷娜・圣帕特里克这样的五年级学生
a fifth grader like my Raina St. Patrick.
你的底子很好 闺女 你知道吗
You come from good stock, girl, you hear me, huh?
你老爸帅气的长相 还有你老妈的嗓音
Your daddy's looks and your mama's voice.
随你怎么说吧 老黑
Whatever, negro.
- 真恶心 - 哪里"恶心"了
- Gross. - "Gross"?
- 给我亲亲 - 不要
- Give me some sugar. - No, no.
等等 你还想跑...
Wait, wait. You trying to run...
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you. - Love you too.
- 在学校过得愉快 - 好的
- Have a good day at school. - Okay.
好了
All right.
继续练习那首歌啊
Keep practicing that song.
晚上七点在Mulberry and Broome见我好吗
所以我们全搞砸了 是吧
So we got fuckups all around, don't we?
诺马・阿奇斯罗给我们的会面信息是假的
The meeting information from Nomar Arcielo was bogus.
我为此承担全部责任 弗兰基
And I take full responsibility for that, Frankie.
但这远远比不上你们这两个笨蛋
But it's no worse than the potential key
在外面胡作非为的时候
to the whole investigation getting murdered
把整个调查的线索都扼杀了
while you two idiots were sitting outside.
萨克斯 你到底在那儿干什么呢
Saxe, what were you doing there anyway?
你本应该写张逮捕证
You were supposed to write the warrant,
而不是去出外勤
not go out on a field trip.
你还影响了麦迪纳特工的监视
And you distracted Agent Medina from good surveillance.
恕我直言 弗兰基 我觉得你要责备的不是我
All due respect, Frankie I hardly think I'm to blame.
你说得对
You're right.
我们责备得已经够多了
There's enough blame to go around.
但问题是 我们现在怎么办
But the question is, where do we go from here?
如果你是对的
If you were right
阿尼巴尔是惹怒洛沃斯的贩毒商
and Anibal was the distributor Lobos was unhappy with,
那么洛沃斯就有了很大的动机买凶
then Lobos had the biggest motive to call a hit.
如果找到了杀阿尼巴尔的凶手 我们就有机会
If we find Anibal's killer, there's a chance
直接联系到洛沃斯
we could connect Lobos directly.
要想成功 我们得需要纽约警局的配合
We're gonna need NYPD cooperation for that.
祝你好运吧
Good luck with that.
管这个案子的警探 梅雷迪斯・海恩斯
The detective on the case, Meredith Haines,
是个控制欲超强的婊子
is a power-tripping bitch.
同类人才相互了解 萨克斯
Takes one to know one, Saxe.
我会和海恩斯警探谈谈的
I'll talk to Detective Haines.
我再把结果反馈给你
Let you know what I find out.
我开车载你去辖区
I'll drive you to the precinct.
我在那儿有些朋友
I've got some friends over there.
如果海恩斯警探真像他们说得那么混蛋
If Detective Haines is as prickly as they say,
那我最好一个人去
then I'm better off going alone
这样我们可以进行女人间的谈话
so we can talk woman-to-woman.
你去给诺马打电话试试吧
You want to try calling Nomar?
他不接我们的电话
He's not responding to our calls.
好的 但是我们早晚得谈谈
Yeah, okay. But as some point, we need to talk
那天晚上化妆师的问题
about the dresser situation from the other night.
再说吧 好吗
Later, okay?
我们要为我的赎罪日做好准备
We're gearing up for my high holy day.
那是什么宗教的鬼东西吗
That some kind of religious shit?
不是
No.
我们要庆祝我的出道日
We're celebrating the day I got made
二十五年前创建了伟大的索尔达多族
born into the mighty Soldado Nation 25 years ago.
我的伙计们都在胳膊上纹了蛇的纹身
Boys in my crew are getting snake tattoos on their arms
这样他们可以尊敬我 比沃拉
so they can honor me, Vibora.
干这行二十来年了
Dos decades in the game.
似乎我们这些人总是
Always seems like guys like us
不需要提防背后的小人
should be able to not look over our shoulder.
那正是阿尼巴尔之死让我和我的伙伴
That's why Anibal's death came as a surprise
惊讶的原因
to me and my partner.
我倒是不怎么惊讶
Can't say it did the same for me.
因为你买的凶吗
Because you made the order?
因为他太肥了 兄弟
Because he's straight up fat, man.
你有没有见过那混蛋吃东西的样子
You ever see that motherfucker eat?
我和你一样 是个生意人
I'm a businessman like you.
我不希望我们有人死掉
I don't wish death on any man,
除非能让我受益
except if it benefits my pockets.
你是不是想接手泰诺人的地盘
Maybe you're trying to take over the Tainos' turf.
我维持我自己地盘的麻烦就够多了
I got enough trouble maintaining my own territory.
我不想扩张
I don't want to expand.
你在中国人地盘上谈的那些
What about that shit you were talking
是什么意思 关于另一个联系的
at the Chinese spot, about another connect?
我认识一个家伙 他又认识另一个
I know a guy who knows a guy.
但那不是你产品质量的问题
But it's not your product's quality.
别废话
你是来这里指控我什么的吗
You're here to accuse me of something or not?
因为刚在不久前 你来我这里寻求帮助
Because not too long ago, you came to me for help,
我把你的团伙稳住了
and I strapped your crew up.
很明显 我们有过节 鲁伊斯
我来这里的原因 兄弟
Reason I'm here, papa.
是出于尊敬
是吗 如果你尊敬我
Yeah?
你就赶紧重新开始放货
You'd open up that damn pipeline again
就像你对罗拉做的那样
like you did for Rolla.
他告诉我你又开始出货了
但我现在连屁都没看见
But I haven't seen shit.
给我几天时间 让我整顿整顿
Give me a couple days to get some things back in order.
你会再嗨起来的
You'll be flying high again.
二十五岁生日快乐
比沃拉
Vibora.
有那么一下子 我还以为
For a minute there, you had me thinking
你不会杀了他呢
you weren't gonna kill him.
那个混蛋当着我的面撒谎
Motherfucker straight up lied to my face,
难道不是吗 汤米
didn't he, Tommy?
我知道他见了洛沃斯 想扩展自己的地盘
Knowing damn well he met with Lobos about stepping up.
早就告诉你 一直是鲁伊斯指使的这件事
Told you it was Ruiz all along.
是啊 但是你还说是阿尼巴尔
Yeah, except when you said it was Anibal.
除了那个 我不管
Except then. I don't care.
现在我只想杀了那混蛋
Now I just want to kill a motherfucker.
嘿 肖恩 你准备好大干一场了吗
Yo, Shawn. You ready to finally get your dick wet?
- 汤米 - 没关系的 叔叔
- Tommy. - No, it's cool, Uncle G.
我想帮帮忙
I want to help.
我有问你话么 肖恩 呃? 他还没准备好
Did I ask you anything, Shawn, huh? He ain't ready.
嘿 这孩子在会议上可是应付自如啊 鬼魂
Hey, the kid handled himself at the meeting, Ghost.
现在不正应该让他更进一步
Ain't it time we let him step it up
就像他父亲曾经和我们一起做的那样?
like his dad did with us?
这孩子还没准备好
Kid ain't ready.
好吧 你可以走了
All right, get out of here.
你发什么神经了 啊? 脑子坏了吗?
What's wrong with you man, huh? What's wrong?
他怎么可能就准备好了?
How's he gonna get ready?
给你当司机根本就不可能让他做好准备
Driving you around ain't prepping him for no real shit.
鲁伊斯很难对付
Ruiz is too hard of a target.
肖恩还太嫩了 他会被杀死的
Shawn's green. He'll get himself killed.
等卡南一年后放出来了
How the fuck we supposed to explain to Kanan,
发现儿子和钱都没了
who gets out in a year, that he's coming home
我们要怎么向他解释?
to no money and no son?
好吧 我会干净利落地把这事解决的
Fine. I'll do it fast and clean.
鲁伊斯不会知道是谁干的
Ruiz won't know what hit him.
不 我不希望我们中的任何人
Nah, I don't want any of our hands
沾染这件破事 好吗?
getting dirty on this, okay?
我们要把这事外包 这样一旦有什么差池
We need to outsource, so we have plausible deniability
我们也不用承担责任
in case something goes wrong.
我做事绝对他妈的万无一失
I do it, ain't shit gonna go wrong.
重要的是这事就此打住 好吗?
The important thing is it stops, all right?
事情一旦完成
The streets don't need to know we did it,
不必让所有人都知道是我们做的
so long as it gets done.
好 你想教训袭击我们的人 他妈的
Fine. You want to blow loot. Fuck it.
我会叫些厉害角色来的
I'll just call in the dreads.
很好 怎么了?
Good. What?
我只是一直在想如果卡南在这的话
I just can't help but think none of this shit
这些该死的家伙根本就不敢欺负我们
would be doing down if Kanan were here.
如果卡南在这的话 我们还在街角干活呢
If Kanan were here, we'd still be working the corner.
开心点
Cheer up.
一切都会结束的 我们还能继续正常做生意
It'll all be over, it can go back to business
- 就像你想的那样 对吧? - 对的
- the way you want it, right? - Right.
对吗?
Right?
对
Right.
我只想谈一下阿尼巴尔・桑塔利斯的谋杀案
I just want to talk about Anibal Santalises's murder.
只要给我你手头的资料 我就会给你
Give me what you have, and I'll give you
任何你用来处理这案子所需要的联邦资料
whatever federal resources you need to clear this case.
而且所有的荣誉都归你
And you'll get all the credit.
受害人的喉咙被割断
The victim's throat was slashed,
他的胸腔有被三叉戟砸过的痕迹
and he was gouged in his chest in the shape of a trident.
索尔达多族的名片
Calling card of the Soldado Nation.
这几乎不可能去证实
It's damn near impossible to confirm.
索尔达多族的不太和外人说话
Soldados don't so much as talk to outsiders.
如果我能给你提供一个内部人选呢
And what if I can get you an insider?
我在听呢
I'm listening.
我需要你帮我找到他
I'll just need your help finding him.
为什么我在这见到你一点都不惊讶呢?
Why am I not surprised to see you here?
我可以去曼哈顿128个夜总会中的任何一个
I could've gone to any of 128 nightclubs in Manhattan.
但你却在真相正襟危坐
Yet you wound up right here at Truth.
当我的客户知道我在后台发现了什么的时候
My clients signed off on your nightclub
他们都很赞同在你的夜总会办活动
when they found out what I was getting on the back end.
你到底发现了什么?
What exactly is that?
让你的员草拟合同吧
Have your people draw up a contract.
四个派对全给你来办
You're getting all four parties.
你应该知道当西蒙斯特恩
You should know that Simon Stern
知道自己估价低了的时候
fired his entire event-management team
就解散了他整个的项目管理团队
when he found out that he was underbid.
你并没结交什么朋友
You're not making any friends.
这并不是个人事情 只是生意而已 辛西娅
It's not personal, just business, Cynthia.
目前是这样
For now.
恭喜你 詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克
Congratulations, James St. Patrick.
很多大人物这一季节
Every boldface name in town is gonna walk
都会来到这里
through those doors this season.
好好发挥
Well played.
谢谢 辛西娅・谢里丹
Thank you, Cynthia Sheridan.
期待与你共事
I look forward to working together.
给我来点汤
I'd like to order some soup.
我们现在只供应鱼茶
Right now the only thing we have is fish tea.
我只想喝山羊汤
I had my heart set on some mannish water.
对不起 山羊汤已经卖完了
Sorry. We out of that at the moment.
为什么你不看看菜单
But why you don't look at the menu and see
也许你可以点些别的什么
if there's anything else you want to order?
我希望过两天能喝到汤
I was hoping to get some in the next two days.
我会和我儿子说的
Let me talk to me son,
如果他做好了我会通知你的
and contact you when he make another batch.
# 他们显而易见 #
They stand out a mile
你女儿试演哪个角色
What part is your daughter auditioning for?
她也试演安妮
She's also going out for Annie.
这是苏西的错
That must be Suzie's fault.
她去年也是女声领唱
She played the female lead last year too,
尽管她当时只是五年级的学生
even though she was only in fifth grade.
这一定让其他女孩觉得她们也有希望
Must make the other girls think they have a shot.
# 笑容是 #
But you're never fully dressed
# 你最美的妆容 #
without a smile
谢谢 苏西 唱得好
Thank you, Suzie. Nicely done.
雷娜...
Raina...
我感觉很抱歉
I just would hate for your daughter
让你的女儿燃起希望
to get her hopes up.
雷娜没问题的
Raina will be just fine.
# 嘿 流浪汉 嘿 与世格格不入的人 #
Hey, hobo man, hey, dapper Dan
# 你们各有千秋 但是 老兄 #
you've both got your style, but, brother
# 笑容才是 #
you're never fully dressed
# 你们最好的妆容 #
without a smile
# 你们的服装也许... #
your clothes may be...
给你的
For you.
实际上 我...
Actually, I'm...
这是事先吩咐好的
I was told to have this waiting for you.
你好
我是卡洛斯
瞧瞧你啊
你经常请陌生人喝酒吗 卡洛斯
不
No.
这可是第一次
让一个女士独饮可不太礼貌哦
It's not polite to make a lady drink alone.
我只想记住今晚发生的一切
I just want to remember everything that happens tonight.
你不觉得这样很冒昧吗?
Aren't you presumptuous?
你做什么工作的 卡洛斯?
What line of work are you in, Carlos?
我是个卖东西的
I'm a salesman.
喔 你都卖些什么
Oh. So what do you sell?
我卖人...
I sell people...
一个幻想
a fantasy.
这对我来说太真实了
That feels a little too real to me.
嗨
Hey.
来吧 别这样
Come on, don't do that.
呆在这...
Stay here...
此时此刻...
in the moment...
就你和我
you and me.
杰米?
Jamie?
谁是杰米?
Who's Jamie?
我们以前来过这吗?
Have we been here before?
我以为你早忘了
I didn't think you'd remember.
我存下全部家当带你来这个城市
I saved all my money to bring you to the city
然后就没钱回去了
and then could barely afford the tokens to get back.
我要发狂了...
I was going crazy...
不知道什么时候吻你才最合适
trying to decide the right moment to kiss you.
现在怎么样?
How about now?
为什么每次你一来我家
Why is our fridge the first place you start
都会先打开我们的冰箱?
every time you come over here?
这里对于一个皮条客来说太难了
It's hard out here for a pimp.
呃 啊 别吃
Mm-hmm. Uh-huh, don't start.
你知道鬼魂是如何获得关于手下的消息的
You know how Ghost gets about his junior's.
他本该九点在这见我的
He was supposed to meet me here at 9:00.
他迟到了 这他妈的是他的错
He's late. It's his fucking fault.
你有没有觉得鬼魂最近经常玩失踪
You noticing Ghost has been M.I.A. a lot lately?
能再给我点这个吗?
Can you get more of this shit?
你还要多少 小伙子?
How much do you need, boy?
这个...
It's just...
我认识了一个女孩
I got a girl.
我在想着也许我可以带她来吃晚餐
I was thinking maybe I'd bring her by for dinner.
这有点不对劲
Something ain't right.
当你提到某个女孩 你一定是有哪里不正常了
You must be coming down with something
更别说
if you claiming girls,
要带姑娘来吃晚饭
let alone want to bring 'em by here.
我喜欢这妞 而且我想带她来吃晚饭
I like this chick, and I want to bring her to dinner
让你看看她怎么样
to see you what you think.
别小题大做了
Stop making such a federal case of it.
你想让我帮你选女孩 汤米?
You want me to pick your girl for you, Tommy?
怎么 难道我要让我妈帮我选么?
What, I'ma let my mom do it?
听着 T 我尊重你的意见
Look, T, I respect your opinion.
你是否喜欢霍莉意义重大
If you like Holly, that means a lot.
好吧
All right.
明天带她来吧
Bring her by tomorrow.
我会炸一些鸡肉或别的吃的
I'll fry up some chicken or something.
哇！就像以前那样
Ooh! Like old times.
像以前你吃光我所有事物的时候
Like old times you eating up all my food,
- 这就是我所理解的 - 嗯 嗯
- that's what it is. - Mmm, mmm.
怎么了 安琪
What's wrong, Angie?
来吧 和我说说
Come on, talk to me.
我们从八年级开始就是朋友了
We've been friends since the eighth grade.
如果你不告诉我你在想些什么
If you can't tell me what's on your mind,
那我们之间就真有问题了
we got real problems.
我想知道我们为什么在这里
I want to know what we're doing here.
只是为了上床吗?
Are we just fucking?
你就是这么想的?
Is that what you think?
- 我不知道该怎么想 - 那就别想
- I don't know what to think. - Maybe don't think.
别说这话 男人总这么说
Don't say that. Men always say that.
听着 昨晚的事就算了
Look, last night was last night.
但如果我们今天又... 那我就要当真了
But if this happens again, then I'm making a choice...
是我要当真了
I am making a choice...
此时此刻
right here, right now...
我要和你在一起
with you.
这是什么?
What is this?
这翅膀?
The wing?
很早就有了
That's something I got a long time ago.
我想要飞走
I wanted to fly away...
逃开
escape.
我知道你不会理解
I'm sure you wouldn't understand.
不 我理解
No, I understand.
因为远离 我失去了很多
I missed a lot, being away.
你现在熟练多了
Oh, you're better at that now.
人是会变的
Some things have changed.
这些都是什么呀?
What's all this?
你知道那个秀 强迫性囤积症患者吗?
You know that show Hoarders?
那是我妈
That's my mom.
那些是都是她的老古董
It's her oldies and goodies collection.
我把这些从她的地下室拿出来消磨时间
I took it out her basement to spin.
在什么上? 留声机吗?
On what, a record player?
是啊
Hell, yeah.
那样听音乐最好了
It's the best way to listen to music.
来
Here...
听听这个
Check this out.
我妈妈从前超爱播这首
My mother used to play this song to death.
我没听过这歌 谁唱的?
I never heard this. Who is this?
斯莫基・罗宾逊 你听说过奇迹吗?
Smokey Robinson. You know, the Miracles?
跟着我
Stick with me.
我会教你很多东西
I'll teach you a lot.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你来我家吃饭吧 顺便见见我的家人
I want you to come to dinner and meet my family.
见你妈妈?
Your mother?
不
No.
我的家人
My family.
他归你了
He's all yours.
我早该猜到这些该死的控告背后是你
I should've known you were behind these bullshit charges.
我没想到你是个虐待狂 我受够了
妈咪
Mami.
你没回我电话
You didn't return my calls.
作为一个女孩子 我还能怎么办?
What's a girl to do?
那是我的信号覆盖问题
It's that damn coverage plan I'm on.
都是电话公司害的
Phone company's a bitch.
所以关于那个会议你了我个假情报?
So are you for feeding me fake intel about that meeting.
本来是有个会的
Nah, there was a meeting.
但最后一刻换地方了
The place got switched at the last moment.
当然换了
Of course it did.
我们没什么好说的了
We're done here.
他们把那事儿解决了
They hashed that shit out.
现在比沃拉和分销商又联系上了
Now Vibora's gonna hook up with the distributor again,
我们的毒品储备在恢复
restock our drug supply.
就他妈的时间问题了
Fucking time.
这么说你是认真的?
So you're serious?
真的有那个会?
That meeting actually happened?
我怎么说来着?
That's what I said, isn't it?
你总是不相信别人 女巫
You got trust issues, bruja.
找人看看吧
See someone about that.
我们需要你去接近鲁伊斯
We need to get you close to Ruiz
这样你就能认出那个分销商了
so you can identify this distributor.
我地位还没高到能知道那些东西
I'm not high enough on the depth chart to find out.
放屁 你地位高得
Bullshit, you were high enough
都能和洛沃斯一起组织会议了
to set up that meeting with Lobos.
而当搞砸了的时候 我也...
And when that went south, I did too...
付出了血的代价
in terms of juice.
好吧 现在是你扳回来的机会
Well, here's your chance to get it back.
根据资料
According to our files,
鲁伊斯的赎罪日就要到了
Ruiz's high holy day is coming up.
那个派对我会去
I'm going to the party.
但我没办法接近他们的核心
But I won't get anywhere near the inner circle.
我把你弄这儿来的 对吧?
I got you here, didn't I?
所以怎么把你弄那儿去就让我来想吧
Let me worry about getting you in there.
没事的 宝贝
It's okay, baby.
没关系
It's all right.
没事
It's okay.
怎么了?
What happened?
学校打电话来
The school called.
蕾娜没得到那个演出角色
Raina didn't get the part in the play.
我不懂他们为什么不选我
I don't know why they didn't pick me.
我尽力了
I did my best.
来这儿 宝贝女儿
Come here, baby girl.
这根本就不公平
It's totally unfair that's why.
蕾娜是那个舞台上唱得最好的
Raina was the best singer on that stage,
但他们却把机会给了那个白人小女孩
and they gave it to the little white girl.
塔莎
Tasha.
他们应该选她的
They should've picked her,
而不是苏西・斯宾塞
not Suzie Spencer.
我知道努力追求却没能得到
I know how disappointing it is to work hard
是多么令人失望
for something and not get it.
她为了这个角色拼尽全力
She busted her ass on this,
而他们却夺走了她的希望
and they took it from her.
生活中有很多事不是你一次就能得到的
Everything you want in life you don't get the first time.
你都要坚持追寻下去
You got to keep going for it.
- 您这么想? - 因为我知道
- You think? - I know.
你继续练习
You keep practicing,
我相信下次你一定会是主演
and next year you will be the lead, I'm sure of it.
好吧 爸爸
Okay, daddy.
这才是我的乖女儿 给我个拥抱
That's my girl. Give me some sugar.
我知道这次你不会再逃走了
I know you're not gonna run from me this time.
这是学校的决定
Her school made a decision.
而且是个错误的决定
And it was the wrong decision.
我们要做点什么才行
We need to do something about it.
生活不会一帆风顺
And that happens sometimes in life.
我们应该让她有所准备
We're supposed to prepare her for that.
我们不能把每个该死的错都改过来！
We can't go around correcting every goddamn wrong!
但我们也不能把这页翻过去然后
And we can't roll over and chalk up everything
记下所有的损失
as a loss either.
我不会让蕾娜重蹈我的覆辙
I'm not letting Raina go through the same shit I did.
就因为你没能成为真命天女
Just because you didn't make it into Destiny's Child
不代表我们的女儿也和你一样被人家设计了
don't mean somebody's out to get our daughter.
滚你的蛋 鬼魂
Fuck you, Ghost.
你知道我妈对我做了什么
You know what my mother did to me,
她对我说 我永远不可能成功
telling me I would never make it.
因为她我才放弃的
I gave up because of her.
现在我们不是在讨论你的歌唱生涯
This ain't about your singing career.
是关于蕾娜的 我绝不会让她放弃
It's about Raina, and I'm not telling her to give up
相反
the opposite.
但她不可能总是赢 这就是生活
But she's not always gonna win, and that's life.
你得放手 行吗? 别管它了
You need to let this shit go, okay? Leave it alone.
听到了吗? 别管这事儿了
You hear me? Leave it alone.
我们说清楚了吧?
Are we clear?
我们今晚和汤米还有他的女友一起晚餐
We're having dinner with Tommy and his girl tonight.
你一定要在场
Just make sure you're here.
汤米有女朋友了? 什么时候的事?
Tommy got a girlfriend? Since when?
走吧 肖恩
Let's go, Shawn.
和汤米去参加的会面怎么样?
So how'd it go at the meeting with Tommy?
是在郊外... 还不错
It was good... being out in the field.
是吗
Yeah.
听着 伙计 我知道你想参与行动
Listen, man, I know you want to get in the action
- 就像你父亲那样 - 没错
- and be like your old man. - No doubt.
我懂 我也曾经感同身受
I get it. Felt the same way.
你父亲把我带进圈里
Your pops brought me in the game,
事无巨细地教我
schooled me on everything.
谨遵一言九鼎
Make sure your word is your bond.
绝不背叛朋友
Never turn your back on your friends
最重要的是 知道什么时候该开口
and most importantly, know when to talk
什么时候该闭嘴
and when not to.
上帝并不是平白无故给你两只耳朵和一张嘴的
God gave you two ears and one mouth for a reason.
今天你自告奋勇要去取一个人性命
You volunteered to take a man's life today.
这是你想要的吗?
Is that what you want?
我已经准备好
I'm ready to step up.
如果你想要街上的门面生意
If you want the street side of the business,
可以 但是我说行的时候才行
it'll happen, but not until I say so.
明白吗?
Understood?
是的 老板
Yes, sir.
因为在你接手那些之前
Because before you get out there,
我会像你爸爸那样
it'll be like your dad.
我必须要很确定 百分之一百确定
I got to be sure, 100% sure,
我可以把我的人生 我的全部都交托你才行
I can trust you with my life, with everything.
叔叔 我支持你
I got your back, Uncle G...
百分之百的
100%.
你喜欢这种布料吗?
You like this fabric?
是的 很紧致 你还要再做一件吗?
Yeah, it's tight. You getting another one?
不 你会有一件
No. You are.
肖恩 参与行动是一回事
Acting the part is one thing, Shawn.
你也得看起来像那样的人
You got to look the part as well.
比沃拉・鲁伊斯有一个毒蛇纹身啊
Vibora Ruiz has a thing for poisonous snakes, huh?
他好几次被抓到走私进口
Been caught smuggling illegal species
非法物种
into the country a couple times.
你在洲际交易所有认识人吗?
You know anyone over at Ice?
我认识一个海关的 怎么了?
Yeah, I got a customs guy. Why?
诺马证实了
Nomar confirmed the meeting
分销商确实召开了那个会议
with the distributor actually happened.
我们要找的这个人还活着
The guy we've been looking for is still alive.
我打算让我的线人去确认他的身份
And I'm gonna get my C.I. to I.D. him.
这个人刚毁了整个部门
That guy just screwed over the whole goddamn department,
然后你要再次利用他?
and you're talking about using him again?
下一步 我有让洛沃斯
Next to you, I got the biggest hard-on
更想要的东西
for Lobos in this place.
这次是我们最好的线索
And this is the best lead either of us has.
所以让我们集中资源解决他
So let's pool our resources and bust his ass.
好吧
All right.
如果我为你这么做
If I do this for you,
也许你可以告诉我一个事
maybe you can clear something up for me.
好的
Sure.
你和诺克斯特工交往多长时间了?
How long have you been fucking Agent Knox?
什么?
Excuse me?
我是被训练来观察人的卧底
I'm an undercover agent trained to read people.
很明显你们之间有事发生
Obviously there's something going on between you two.
什么事都没有
There's nothing going on.
随便吧
Whatever.
梅丽莎 你见霍莉了吗?
Melissa, have you seen Holly?
她又因病请假了
She called in sick, again.
我想是她觉得她和老板上过床
I guess she thinks 'cause she's fucking the boss,
就不用遵守规定了
she doesn't have to follow the rules.
等等 什么?
Wait. What?
不是黑人是白人汤米
Not the black one the white guy, Tommy.
我说他是个混蛋
You ask me, he's an asshole.
这点我不反对
No argument from me there.
老板想让我们今晚把秘密贵宾通道打开
Boss wants us starting the secret V.I.P. entrances tonight,
我需要她在这
and I need her here.
我打电话给她
I got to call her.
追踪这些混蛋职员
Chasing down these fucking employees.
先生对不起
I'm sorry, sir.
我们今天不对外开放
We're not open to the public yet.
没事
It's okay.
我不是外人
I'm not the public.
斯特恩先生
Mr. Stern.
- 你在干什么? - 什么?
- Are you kidding me? - What?
你现在还没洗澡?
You haven't gotten a shower yet?
宝贝 我们有很多时间
Babe, we got plenty of time.
他们会在那等着的
They're gonna be here any minute.
这就是他们为什么总是说黑人
You're the reason why they say black folks
总是迟到
are always late.
不 他们说黑人总是迟到
No, they say black folks are always late
因为我们总是迟到
'cause we always late.
哦 不
Hell, no.
今晚不行
Not tonight.
喂
Hello.
晚上好 圣帕特里克太太
Good evening, Mrs. St. Patrick.
我是真相夜总会的约书亚・坎托斯
It's Joshua Kantos from Truth.
我有一条很重要的信息告诉老板
I left a message for the boss on his cell phone,
我想跟他说说
but it's very important that I talk to him.
- 他现在可以接电话吗? - 他在洗澡
- Is he available? - He's in the shower.
他有空的话我叫他打过去
I'll have him return when he gets a minute.
这非常重要
This is very important.
总是很重要
It always is, Kantos.
我一定会告诉他的
I'll be sure to let him know.
拜托了 圣帕特里克太太
Please, Mrs. St. Patrick.
我得告诉他 这很重要
It's very important that I get a hold
好了 宝贝 刚才门卫说了
all right, babe, the doorman just buzzed.
汤米和他的伴侣在路上
Tommy and his date are on their way up.
顺便说一下 你看见我手机了吗?
By the way, you see my cell phone?
是的 在这 宝贝
Oh, yeah. It's right here, babe.
- 哦 酷 - 你先在门口等着 好吗?
- Oh, cool. - You get the door, okay?
我要去梳洗一下
I got to go freshen up a bit.
好的
All right.
- 嗨 汤米 - 你好 G
- Hey, Tommy. - What's up, G?
我想你们已经认识了
I think y'all know each other.
霍莉 俱乐部的霍莉
Holly... Holly from the club.
很高兴认识你 圣帕特里克先生
Nice to see you, Mr. St. Patrick.
你可以叫他詹姆斯
Oh, you can call him James.
你好
Hello.
- 我亲爱的妻子 - 我是塔莎
- My lovely wife. - Hi. I'm Tasha.
汤米跟我说了很多你的事
Hi. Tommy told me all about you.
我没有想到圣帕特里克先生
I had no idea Mr. St. Patrick,
是他经常谈到的
the big boss, was actually the brother
老板哥哥
he's always talking about.
该喝点了 我来倒酒
Yo, it's time to drink. I'll pour.
T带霍莉参观下吧
T, why don't you show Holly around.
我来拿你的外套
I'll take your coat.
天啊
Holy shit.
这个衣橱比我的公寓还大
This thing is bigger than my apartment.
这是LV的吗?
Is this Louis Vuitton?
这个要花大概一千美元呢
This thing costs, like, $1,000.
两千美元
2,000.
我丈夫在上次出差时候买给我的
My husband brought it back from his last business trip.
这才是我想要的
That's what I want.
这才是真爱
That is real love.
不是因为礼物
It's not about the gift.
是因为他能想到你
It's about the fact that he's thinking of you,
而且他觉得你值得花钱
and he thinks you're worth the money.
我确定汤米会给你任何你要的东西
I'm sure Tommy will get you anything you ask for.
要汤米买个包
Tommy wouldn't know that bag
你得揍他一拳才知道
if I hit him in the face with it.
你们做到了
You guys got it made.
我想是的
Yeah, I guess so.
不错
Nice.
好东西 干杯
The good stuff. Cheers.
干杯
Cheers.
我对你们重振旗鼓 经营自己的夜总会
I am really impressed with how you bounced back,
印象深刻
got your own club.
我确实有一个问题问你
I do have one question for you.
你怎么这么快筹集到钱的?
How did you raise the money so fast?
先生 我只是个有限合伙人
I'm only a limited partner here, sir.
那是詹姆斯・圣・帕特里克的钱
It's James St. Patrick's money.
但你是这个地方经营
But you're the reason this place
这么成功的原因
is turning out to be so successful.
不能这么说
I couldn't say that.
James知道对于一个从没经营过
For a guy who's never been in the business,
生意的人该做什么
James knows what he's doing.
我们每天晚上的爆满 特别是
We're full every night, extremely tight door,
顾客每一次进来
and once they're in, every kind of customer
他们都有特别的对待
gets specific treatment.
他们上次点了什么酒 喜欢坐哪个位置
The drinks they ordered last time, the booth they loved,
他们想上的服务员
the waitress they wanted to fuck.
你对这很了解么 不是吗?
Well, you'd know about that, wouldn't you?
我们这里有很好的体系
We've got a great system here, sir.
鉴于只有我们两个人
Seeing as it's just the two of us,
圣帕特里克是做什么生意的?
what is St. Patrick's deal?
他来自哪? 他的背景是什么?
Where's he from? What's his background?
我试着调查他 但是什么没查到
I tried looking into him myself and came up empty.
他之前是做什么的?
What did he do before this?
还记得JSP和汤米-汤姆斯吗?
Remember JSP and Tommy-Toms?
别告诉我汤米- 汤姆斯是个艺名
Oh, please tell me Tommy-Toms was not your stage name.
那是八十年代 每个人都有两个名字
It was the '80s. Everybody had two names.
丽莎丽莎 马基马克
Lisa Lisa, Marky Mark.
还有汤米汤姆斯
And Tommy-Toms.
这名字听起来像是破中国餐厅的
That shit sounded like a bad Chinese restaurant.
你不会就坐在这让我们说话吧
You're not gonna sit there and just blaze us up like that?
我们来段说唱吧 B
Yo, let's bust out a verse, B.
我们第一次见面我丈夫就唱这首饶舌
My husband used to always do this rap about how we first met.
加油 汤米
Go for it, Tommy.
我不记得歌词了
I don't remember the words.
# 我爱她 她也喜欢 #
I like it, she... she love it
# 毫不犹豫 我得加把劲 #
no hesitation, I had to push up on it
# 我爱她 她也喜欢 #
I like it, she... she love it
# 毫不犹豫 毫不犹豫 #
no hesitation, no hesitation
# 她惊人的美让我窒息 #
her breathtaking beauty had me gasping
# 我与她 就是这么简单 #
me and her together, this was simple math
# 至少对我而言 命运驱使吗 #
and at least for me, it was destiny?
# 我跟我的女孩 #
was me and baby girl
别这样
Oh, come on, man,
你知道我很长时间不唱了
you know I hung my mic up a long time ago.
扫兴
Party pooper.
- 这就是我的丈夫 - 好吧
- That's my husband. - Fine.
如果你不唱 我得给你找点事做做
If you ain't gonna rap, I need you to work a bit.
那个俱乐部让他们很忙啊
That club sure keeps them busy, huh?
忙得超乎想象
Like you couldn't imagine.
我能去下洗手间吗?
Mind if I you use your bathroom?
好的 在走廊尽头的右面
Sure. It's right down the hall.
我们明天约了牙买加人
We're all set with the Jamaicans for tomorrow.
我没告诉你别搞服务员吗?
Didn't I tell you not to fuck the merchandise?
让我们放到台上说
Let's get one thing straight from jump.
不用你来对我说教 我又不是小孩
You don't tell me shit. I'm not a fucking child.
你表现得就像是
You're acting like one
带着她来表演
bringing breezies over to my house for show-and-tell?
这里不是那些乌合之众呆的地方
This ain't some skank-ass broad.
霍莉不一样 她是特别的
Holly's different. She's special.
今晚她是 明天早上也许是
Tonight she is. Tomorrow morning she might be.
你他妈可饶了我吧
Give me a fucking break.
拜托 汤米 你和我都知道
Come on, Tommy, you... you and I both know
你到一个月或者一年以后就感觉不到了
you ain't gonna feel that way in a month or a year.
你怎么关心我和谁上床?
Why you care who I'm boning anyway?
因为你上了给我工作的人
Because you're fucking someone who works at my business,
这关系到我的生意
which makes this about my business.
上次我查过 我们是五五分成
Last I checked, this was a 50-50 partnership,
就是说霍莉是你的员工也是我的
which makes Holly just as much my employee as she is yours.
听着 伙计 意思就是我也不能上她
Look, man, that just means I can't fuck her either.
但是你最好不要告诉她咱们其他的事
But you better not have told her about our other thing.
这又不是我第一次 你觉得我是傻子吗?
This ain't my first rodeo. Do you think I'm fucking stupid?
部门在这上面挥金如土?
The department splurged on this?
我得承认这是不寻常的花费
I may have submitted it as a slightly different expense.
如果我们抓到洛沃斯没人会注意的
We get Lobos, no one will care.
你操控纽约警察局和海关?
You manipulated NYPD and Customs?
你一点不在乎协议 不是吗?
You don't give two shits about protocol, do you?
就像你刚刚在弗兰基鼻子底下和诺克斯上床
Just like you fucking Knox right under Frankie's nose.
这次不会了
Not this again.
我打赌他一定给你口交了
鼻子都快伸进去了吧
你为什么在乎?
Why do you care?
因为我不想让你和他在一起了
'Cause I don't want you to fuck up again.
如果诺克斯是上星期让你分心的原因
If Knox's dick is the reason you got distracted last week,
- 我想知道 - 你给萨克斯吹箫了吗?
- I want to know. - Were you sucking Saxe off?
所以才没看到阿尼巴尔被杀?
Is that why you missed Anibal's doer?
你的头在仪表下面
Your head was under the dashboard,
萨克斯闭着双眼
Saxe's eyes were closed.
我想抓住洛沃斯那个混蛋
我也是
你钥匙去哪了?
Where's your fucking key?
我听见你的声音了
I heard voices.
我想确定岸上安全了
I wanted to make sure the coast was clear.
我有办法让你成为
I got you just the ticket to get you
索尔达多族高级委员会的一员
in the high council of the Soldado Nation.
你必须提供你自己或者一吨毒品
You must be offering yourself or a ton of drugs,
因为妹子和白粉是唯一
'cause pussy and powder are the only things
- 让我接近鲁伊斯的东西 - 哇
- that'll get me next to Ruiz. - Whoa.
你能注意点儿言语吗? 这还有个女士呢
Can you watch your mouth? There's a lady present.
这他妈是谁?
Who the fuck is this?
诺马 这是乔・冈萨雷斯
Nomar, this is Joe Gonzales,
局里的爬行动物专家
a reptile specialist with the department.
你为什么总会带新人来?
Why you always bringing new people?
这就是个选A选B的问题
This is supposed to be an "A" and "B" situation.
爬行动物专家应该消失
Reptile man needs to see his way out.
好的 但是直到我向你展示...
Okay, but not until I show you...
怎么处理这个才行
how to handle this.
哇
Whoa.
今晚能见你吗
霍莉!
Holly!
我拿着你的外套! 快点儿!
I got your coat! Come on!
我们离开这
We out of here.
可以
再见 塔莎
Bye, Tasha.
再见 詹姆斯
Bye, James.
明天工作见
Uh, I'll see you at work tomorrow.
再见 T
See you, T.
谢谢你
Thank you.
没事
Yeah.
他们像科斯比秀一样 你知道吗?
They're like the Cosby Show, you know?
她似乎拥有一切...
She seems to have it all...
而不是事实上她的老公背叛她
other than the fact that her husband's cheating on her.
你刚才说啥?
What did you just say?
前不久的一个晚上
I was dropping some receipts off
我把一些收据落在办公室了
in the office the other night,
然后我走进去撞见圣帕特里克先生
and I walked in on Mr. St Patrick
正在干一个拉丁美女
nailing some latina.
你他妈的管好自己的事
You need to mind your own fucking business.
- 我做什么了? - 闭他妈嘴吧!
- What did I do? - Just shut the fuck up!
该死!
Damn!
汤米!
Tommy!
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不该说这些
I shouldn't have said that.
你抱歉什么呀?
What are you apologizing for?
这让你愤怒了
That made you angry.
我不喜欢看见这样的你
And I don't like seeing you that way.
我喜欢你感觉好的时候
I like it when you feel good.
- 你去哪了? - 你不会相信的
- Where you been? - You're not gonna believe this.
但是麦迪纳最终入伙了
But Medina finally got on board,
在诺马的事上协助我
helping me with a Nomar thing.
诺马明晚应该在鲁伊斯的聚会上
Nomar should be in at Ruiz's party tomorrow night.
听着 我不想当个混蛋
Look, I'm not trying to be a dick,
但是理论上讲 诺马是我的线人
but technically, Nomar is my C.I.
所以 如果你想让麦迪纳加入
So, if you want to let Medina in,
你至少应该先询问一下我
you should have at least consulted me first.
我知道你郁闷 但是我们能该天再谈吗?
I know you're upset, but can we talk some other time?
因为我要去见一些朋友要迟到了
Because I'm running late to meet some friends.
好的 当然 改天...
Yeah, sure. Some other time...
例如当你准备好对我坦诚相待时
Like when you're ready to be honest with me.
你知道吗 随时奉陪
You know, whenever that is.
- 格雷格 - 你和 麦迪纳上床了吗?
- Greg. - Are you sleeping with Medina?
什么?
What?
这不像你的一贯作风
It's not like it's not your M.O.
和工作中的人滚床单
To fuck somebody at work.
- 干你 格雷格 - 最近没有
- Fuck you, Greg. - Not lately.
明天我们谈谈这个
We're gonna talk about this tomorrow.
不 不 现在我们就谈谈
No. No, we're gonna talk about this now.
我要走了
I got to go.
我不会让你走出这个门的
I'm not letting you walk out that door.
至少我能告诉我朋友一声我不能去了吗?
Can I at least tell my friends I can't show up?
罗拉 怎么啦?
Rolla, what up?
我听说那个肥男被盯上了
I heard the fat man got marked.
我不知道你把谁给逼疯了 但是
I don't know who you got on them corners, but
摇滚街的凯勒斯准备出手了
rock street Killahz are ready to step up
- 为大家搞定一个? - 没问题
- and take one for the team? - No question.
这次我全给你和那个白人小子留着
I done kept it 100 with you and white boy from the jump.
好的 汤米替我开了会
Good. Tommy filled me in on the meeting.
但是我还是不知道是谁袭击了我们...
But we still haven't found out who's hitting us...
除非你有什么想告诉我的
unless you got something you want to spill.
没有
Negative.
好 泰诺人已经有人顶替了阿尼巴尔
Well, Tainos got Anibal's number two in place already.
我不知道什么原因让他失去地盘
I don't see any reason for him to lose his territory,
除非你打听点儿关键的
unless you doing some serious ear hustling
想要帮我宰了
and want to help me kill
幕后的混蛋
the motherfucker behind this shit.
- 好的 - 好的 再见
- On it. - All right. Later.
抱歉 不能见面了
首先 我没有和麦迪纳
First of all, I'm not fucking Medina
或者其他办公室的人上床
or anyone at the office.
你是说任何人
Anyone else, you mean.
有工作关系的 格雷格
People get into relationships at work, Greg.
但你在办公室一天花二十个小时时
When you spend 20 hours a day together in an office,
这会发生的
it happens.
- 我不是妓女 - 我从来没这么说过
- I'm not a whore. - I never said that.
有意思 我听得很清楚
Funny, I heard it loud and clear.
麦迪纳问我我今天是不是和你上床了
Medina asked me today if I was fucking you.
- 你告诉他什么了? - 什么都没发生
- And what did you tell him? - That nothing was going on.
他这么问是因为
He was asking because I fucked up
我把那天的突袭搞砸了
the raid the other day.
我不想和你吵架 格雷格
I don't want to fight with you, Greg.
我只想抓到洛沃斯然后收工
I just want to catch Lobos and call it a day.
我要和其他那些同事谈话
I got to be able to talk to our other colleagues
你不能这样就认为我跟他们滚床单了
without you thinking I'm sleeping with them.
我要去见我们的线人
I got to be able to meet our C.I.
而你不能死死地盯住我
without you breathing down my neck.
我需要一些空间 格雷格
I got to have some space, Greg.
你知道吗? 你可以尽你所能的把此事
You know what? You can blame this on our jobs
怪罪于我们的工作 但是这是你的问题
as much as you want, but this is a "you" problem.
所以 不管怎样 不管你发生什么
So, whatever it is, whatever's going on with you,
上帝呀 祝你好运
Jesus, good luck.
给你空间
Here's your space.
早 肖恩
Morning, Shawn.
嘿
Hey.
这是新西装吗?
Is that a new suit?
是
Yeah.
让我看看怎么样
Let me see how it looks.
这都是我老公一手包办的吧
This has my husband written all over it.
是 是 过几天我要再去拜访我爹
Yeah, yeah, I'm going to visit my dad again in a few days.
G想让我看起来体面点儿
G wanted me to look nice.
你和幽灵越来越亲近了
You and Ghost are getting pretty close.
你可能是看他来回开车看久了 嗯 肖恩?
You probably see a lot driving him around, huh, Shawn?
这件衣服配你太完美了
This suit fits you perfectly.
我超喜欢这种感觉
And I love how it feels.
我认为他向我隐瞒了什么
I think he's keeping something from me,
我想知道这件事持续多久了
and I want to know how long it's been going on.
真希望我知道你在说什么
Uh, I wish I knew what you were talking about.
嗯 你的谎言太劣质了
Hmm, you're a terrible liar.
我丈夫和汤米之间到底发生了什么?
What's going on between my husband and Tommy?
他们最近有很多分歧
They've been having a lot of disagreements lately.
哪方面的?
Disagreements about what?
告诉我吧
You can tell me.
这将成为你我之间的又一个小秘密
It'll be another one of our little secrets.
我也不太清楚
I don't really know.
那次见面以后
They've been beefing
他们就摩擦不断
ever since we got back from that meeting.
塔莎
Tasha.
肖恩在吗?
Is Shawn out there?
嗯 他在看报
Yeah, he's reading the paper.
早啊老板 你好了?
Morning, boss. You ready?
早 嗯
Morning. Yeah.
- 一天愉快哦 - 你也是
- Have a good day. - You too.
随你
Whatever you want.
过会儿给你回电话
Hey, let me call you back.
你收到我的信儿了?
You got my messages?
啥啊?
What messages?
西蒙・斯特恩昨晚来夜总会了
Simon Stern came into the club last night.
别闹了
You better be shitting me.
就因为你玩失踪 我才得应付斯特恩
You were M.I.A., so I bonded with Stern,
他皮笑肉不笑地跟我讨论
skinning and grinning my way around a conversation
说我们办那些派对的出价低于他
about us underbidding him for those parties.
你是想用他来谋职吗?
You trying to angle to get a job with him, huh?
不 我给你的语音信箱里留言了
No, I left you a message on your voice mail,
并且我以为你在家呢
and I tried you at home.
你老婆说你在洗澡
Your wife said you were in the shower.
该做的我都做了
I did my job.
我既没看到未接来电
I didn't see one missed call
也没收到语音留言 坎托斯
or a fucking voice mail, Kantos.
你就在之前工作的酒吧里
You were hooking V.I.P.s up with bottle girls
用侍酒女郎钓贵宾
at the last club you worked.
脑子被门挤了才有人想用你
No one would hire you with a fistful of 50s.
所以别在这儿给我扮无辜
So don't stand there acting like your ass don't stink,
否则我就把你带到人事主管那儿去
or I'll send you back to your P.O. to air out.
再有下回你他妈直接跳上车
Next time you get in your fucking car
开到我家来 听懂了吗?
and you drive to my fucking house, you hear me?
我听过雷娜的小样 她唱得不错
I heard Raina's audition. She sang well.
显然她还不够好
Obviously not well enough.
这些角色数量有限
These roles are limited
通常只有六年级生才能担任
and typically granted to sixth graders.
除了去年五年级的苏西・斯宾塞
Except Suzie Spencer got the lead last year
担任了主角
as a fifth grader.
可你要知道啊圣帕特里克太太
Mrs. St. Patrick, three generations of Spencers
斯宾塞家有三代都是在我们学校念书
have matriculated through our school.
你肯定明白的
I'm sure you understand.
我们只能这么做
The decision's been made in the matter.
哦 真的吗?
Oh, has it?
- 比沃拉 - 看看谁来了
- Vibora. - Mira quien es.
- 怎么样啊你? - 恭喜恭喜
- How are you? - Felicitaciones.
这是啥?
What's that?
给比沃拉的礼物
A tribute for Vibora.
是这东西啊
This shit.
正合我意
This I love.
你从哪儿搞到的这个啊?
How did you get this in the country?
赎罪日快乐 比沃拉
Happy high holy day, Vibora.
- 祝你幸福 - 谢谢你我的朋友
来 给我一瓶
Venga. Dame la botella.
谢了
Thank you.
在那儿 喝吧 喝吧
Toma ahi. Toma, toma.
安吉拉: 昨晚实在是抱歉 一小时内过来补偿你
一会儿见 宝贝儿
I'll be right back, babe.
宝贝儿 能跟我解释下为啥不告诉我
Uh, babe, you want to tell me why you didn't tell me
坎托斯昨晚来电的事儿呢?
Kantos called last night?
我一定是忘了
I must've forgot,
一直在忙着准备晚饭
with all the running around with the dinner.
我错过了一个和西蒙・斯特恩的重要会晤
I missed a very important meeting with Simon Stern.
对不起啊
I'm sorry.
喂?
Hello?
请问你是?
May I ask who's calling?
雷娜 接电话!
Raina, pick up the phone!
- 爸 妈 我得到那个角色了 - 嗯?
- Mom, dad, I got the part. - What?
是导演 他们之前搞错了
That was the drama director. They made a mistake.
我和苏西一起饰演安妮
I've been double... cast with Suzie to play Annie.
真的吗? 恭喜你啊宝贝儿
What? Congratulations, honey.
噢 我太为你骄傲了
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
你看
Look at that.
我就说会有个好结果的 我的女儿真棒
I told you it would work out in the end, baby girl.
我要通知所有的小伙伴儿!
I got to go call all my friends!
快去吧
Call 'em.
我一会儿就回来
Um, I'll be right back.
牛奶喝完了
We're out of milk.
我们一会儿过来
Cool Runnings:We're heading in.
我好像刚收到你那条四百二十字的短信 T
Yo, I ain't got a 420 text from you in a minute, T.
得好好记下这一刻
Got some extra... good shit to mark the occasion.
你一定要记住
You must really need to hit this.
好啊 可是别再我家楼下出现行吗
Yeah, but don't be rolling up in front of my building.
妈的
Damn.
幽灵讨厌我抽烟
Ghost hates it when I smoke.
去他妈的吧 他不需要知道
Fuck that. He don't need to know.
你和那个叫霍莉的妞儿进展很快嘛
That girl Holly is way too fast for you.
真的吗?
Seriously?
我是说 你喜欢就喜欢吧
I mean, you like her, you like her,
但这只是我的个人观点
but that's just my two cents.
记住了
Noted.
放轻松 我可是专业选手
Relax. I'm a pro with this.
是嘛 好吧 我可没看出来
Yeah, all right, I can't tell.
兄弟 我可是有小孩的人
Nigga, I got kids.
听着 虽然我这样很磨叽
Look, I know I'm starting to sound like a broken record,
但你小子显然没在状态
but your boy's head ain't in the game.
幽灵可总是蓄势待发
You know Ghost is always on some next shit.
得了吧 我们一会儿就到了
Come on, we'll be out your hood in a minute.
有人等着看你的笑话呢
Ain't no one gonna see your ass.
我的意思是 他需要我们来巩固他的地位
I'm just saying, he depends on us to keep him grounded.
但现在却开始对我颐指气使了
But now he's talking to me sideways,
- 把你也无礼极了 - 没有吧
- disrespecting you and shit. - Nah.
别睁眼说瞎话 你昨天可是早就走了
Don't lie to me to my face, you left early the other night
因为你和幽灵打了一架 对吧?
because you and Ghost got into a fight, right?
你觉得幽灵又开始喝酒了吗?
You think Ghost is drinking again?
这事跟喝酒没关 T
This ain't no bottle problem, T.
也许他开始经历
Maybe Ghost is just going through
中年危机了
some sort of midlife crisis.
现在也太早了吧
It's too early for that.
我觉得就是夜总会那破事儿
I think it's just this club shit.
以小见大啊
That's a symptom, not the disease.
幽灵变了 汤米
Ghost is changing, Tommy.
我现在想一定事出有因
I'm starting to think it ain't a temporary thing.
现在人多起来了
It's starting to get crowded.
跟着我 时刻注意周围情况
Stay by me and keep your head on a swivel.
- 干杯 - 干杯
- Salud. - Salud.
另一个
Otra.
我去趟脱衣舞俱乐部
I'll be in the champagne room.
伊莎贝尔: 我想你 你在我爸的派对上吗?
诺马: 嗯 我也想你
伊莎贝尔: 我爸玩得爽不?
他妈的
Shit.
胡里奥!
Julio!
比沃拉受伤了!
Vibora's hurt!
出事儿了!
Something's wrong!
都他妈怎么一回事儿?
What the fuck happened?
你记得我和汤米组过一个说唱组合吗?
You remember Tommy and I had a rap group?
JSP和DJ 汤米... 汤姆斯?
JSP and DJ Tommy... Toms?
你记得我为你写的说唱乐吗?
You remember the rap I made up for you?
# 我喜欢 她... 她喜欢#
I like it, she... she love it
# 不要犹豫 就趁现在 #
no hesitation, I had to push up on it
# 嗯 嗯 我喜欢 嗯 嗯 她喜欢#
uh, uh, I like it, uh, uh, she love it
# 不要犹豫 就趁现在#
no hesitation, I had to push up on it
看来你经商是件好事
It's a good thing you became a businessman.
嘘
Be quiet.
你喜欢它对吧
You know you like it.
是公事 我得接个电话
It's work. I should probably get this.
我去别的屋接
I'll take it in the other room.
汤米 怎么了?
Tommy, what's up?
你需要什么?
What do you need?
诺马刚刚打过来 鲁伊斯遇刺了
Nomar just called. Ruiz has been stabbed.
真的吗?
Are you serious?
鲁伊斯遇刺了 正中胸部
Ruiz got stabbed, right in the chest.
太棒了
Excellent.
显然是诺马跟他在一起
Apparently Nomar's in with him,
他们现在去医院了
and they're headed somewhere to get medical attention.
不是我们雇的牙买加人干的
It wasn't the Jamaicans we hired.
有人跟踪他 现在不见了
Someone went after him and missed.
他没死
He ain't dead.
你在哪儿呢?
Where are you?
我一会儿就到
I'm on my way in right now.
所以说 如果是别人袭击的他
So, if someone else swung at him,
也就是说他不是我们问题的根源
that means he's not the source of our problem after all.
我们得碰个面儿 把事情搞清楚
We got to meet up, sort all this out.
出问题了 我得走了
Work is blowing up. I got to go.